swagvault.com 2013-05-28

# SwagVault Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

SwagVault is committed to protecting your privacy and safeguarding the privacy of your personal data. We recognize the importance of protecting the confidentiality of personal information and take appropriate measures to protect your privacy as well as your personal information. We use the personal information to provide you with better customer support and services. 

How We Collect Information

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, Street Address, ZIP code, and so on. When you register with SwagVault and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Personally Information Security

SwagVault treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. SwagVault does not rent, sell, share or disclose any personally information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on SwagVault' sites with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for non- SwagVault marketing purposes. 

How We Use Information

SwagVault uses the personal information we collect online principally to provide you with the services you have ordered. SwagVault collects personal information to verify the accuracy of your name, billing address, shipping address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date provided, to bill you for products and services purchased and to pay you for products and services sold. SwagVault uses your e-mail address to contact you regarding the status of your order when necessary and to send you a Receipt Purchase/Sale Confirmation and Order Shipping Notification. 

SwagVault may occasionally let you know some information on products, services, special deals and promotions which may be of interest to you. 

Account Protection 

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your SwagVault password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify SwagVault and change your password.
